Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 11: Boxes 636-699
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 11: Boxes 636-699
- ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union), Publication (Box 643, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Report of the General Executive Board, 1981; Publication (Box 643, Folder 4)
    Notes: Second Constitutional Convention
  - Item 2: Convention Proceedings, 1981; Publication (Box 643, Folder 4)
- American Federation of Hosiery Workers, Publication (Box 643, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Report of the Officers and Executive Board, 1939; Publication (Box 643, Folder 5)
    Author: American Federation of Hosiery Workers
    Notes: Twenty-Eighth Annual Convention
- American Federation of Hosiery Workers, Publication (Box 643, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Report to the Thirty-Second Annual Convention, 1943; Publication (Box 643, Folder 6)
- American Federation of Hosiery Workers, Publication (Box 643, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Report to the Thirty-Third Annual Convention, 1944; Publication (Box 643, Folder 7)
- American Federation of Hosiery Workers, Publication (Box 643, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Report to the Thirty-Fourth Annual Convention, 1946; Publication (Box 643, Folder 8)
- American Federation of Hosiery Workers, Publication (Box 643, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Report to the Thirty-Sixth Annual Convention, 1948; Publication (Box 643, Folder 9)
- American Federation of Hosiery Workers, Publication (Box 643, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Report to the Thirty-Seventh Annual Convention, 1949; Publication (Box 643, Folder 10)
- American Federation of Hosiery Workers, Publication (Box 643, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Officers Report, 1950; Publication (Box 643, Folder 11)
    Notes: Thirty-Eighth Annual Convention
- American Federation of Hosiery Workers, Publication (Box 643, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Officers Report, 1951; Publication (Box 643, Folder 12)
    Notes: Thirty-Ninth Annual Convention
- American Federation of Hosiery Workers, Publication (Box 643, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Officers Report, 1952; Publication (Box 643, Folder 13)
    Notes: Forty Annual Convention
- American Federation of Hosiery Workers, Publication (Box 643, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Officers Report, 1953; Publication (Box 643, Folder 14)
    Notes: Forty-First Annual Convention
- American Federation of Hosiery Workers, Publication (Box 643, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Officers Report, 1954; Publication (Box 643, Folder 15)
    Notes: Forty-Second Annual Convention
- American Federation of Hosiery Workers, Publication (Box 643, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Officers Report, 1955; Publication (Box 643, Folder 16)
    Notes: Forty-Third Annual Convention
- American Federation of Hosiery Workers, Publication (Box 643, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Officers Report, 1957; Publication (Box 643, Folder 17)
    Notes: Forty-Fourth Annual Convention
- American Federation of Hosiery Workers, Publication (Box 643, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Officers Report, 1963; Publication (Box 643, Folder 18)
    Notes: Forty-Seventh Annual Convention
- Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, Publication (Box 643, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the Twenty-Second Regular Convention, 1925; Publication (Box 643, Folder 19)
    Author: Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes
- Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, Publication (Box 643, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the Twenty-Third Regular Convention, 1928; Publication (Box 643, Folder 20)
- Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, Publication (Box 643, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the Twenty-Fourth Regular Convention, 1931; Publication (Box 643, Folder 21)
- Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, Publication (Box 643, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the Twenty-Fifth Regular Convention, 1934; Publication (Box 643, Folder 22)
- Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, Publication (Box 643, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the Twenty-Sixth Regular Convention, 1937; Publication (Box 643, Folder 23)
- Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, Publication (Box 643, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the Twenty-Seventh Regular Convention, 1940; Publication (Box 643, Folder 24)
- Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, Publication (Box 643, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the Twenty-Eighth Regular Convention, 1943; Publication (Box 643, Folder 25)
- Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, Publication (Box 643, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the Twenty-Ninth Regular Convention, 1946; Publication (Box 643, Folder 26)
- Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, Publication (Box 644, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the Thirtieth Regular Convention, 1949; Publication (Box 644, Folder 1)
- Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, Publication (Box 644, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the Thirty-First Regular Convention, 1952; Publication (Box 644, Folder 2)
- Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, Publication (Box 644, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the Thirty-Second Regular Convention, 1955; Publication (Box 644, Folder 3)
- Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, Publication (Box 644, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the Thirty-Third Regular Convention, 1958; Publication (Box 644, Folder 4)
- Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, Publication (Box 644, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the Thirty-Fourth Regular Convention, 1962; Publication (Box 644, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: President's Report, 1962; Publication (Box 644, Folder 5)
    Notes: Thirty-Fourth Regular Convention
- Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, Publication (Box 644, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the Thirty-Fifth Regular Convention, 1966; Publication (Box 644, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: President's Report, 1966; Publication (Box 644, Folder 6)
    Notes: Thirty-Fifth Regular Convention
- Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, Publication (Box 644, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the Thirty-Sixth Regular Convention, 1970; Publication (Box 644, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: President's Report, 1970; Publication (Box 644, Folder 7)
    Notes: Thirty-Sixth Regular Convention
- Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, Publication (Box 644, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the Thirty-Seventh Regular Convention, 1974; Publication (Box 644, Folder 8)
- Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, Publication (Box 645, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: President's Report, 1974; Publication (Box 645, Folder 1)
    Notes: Thirty-Seventh Regular Convention
- Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, Publication (Box 645, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Proceedings, 1978; Publication (Box 645, Folder 2)
    Notes: Thirty-Eighth Regular Convention
- Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, Publication (Box 645, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Proceedings, 1982; Publication (Box 645, Folder 3)
    Notes: Thirty-Ninth Regular Convention
- BRSA (Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen of America), Publication (Box 645, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Minutes of the Eleventh Annual and Thirteenth Regular Sessions, 1918; Publication (Box 645, Folder 4)
    Author: BRSA (Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen of America)
- BRSA (Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen of America), Publication (Box 645, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Minutes of the First Biennial and Sixteenth Regular Sessions, 1922; Publication (Box 645, Folder 5)
- BRSA (Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen of America), Publication (Box 645, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Minutes of the Second Biennial and Seventeenth Regular Sessions, 1924; Publication (Box 645, Folder 6)
- BRSA (Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen of America), Publication (Box 645, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Minutes of the Third Biennial and Eighteenth Regular Sessions, 1926; Publication (Box 645, Folder 7)
- BRT (Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen), Publication (Box 645, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the Twenty-Ninth Convention, 1950; Publication (Box 645, Folder 8)
    Author: BRT (Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen)
- BRT (Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen), Publication (Box 645, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the Thirtieth Convention, 1954; Publication (Box 645, Folder 9)
- BRT (Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen), Publication (Box 645, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: President's Report, 1958; Publication (Box 645, Folder 10)
- BRT (Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen), Publication (Box 645, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the Thirty-First Convention, 1960; Publication (Box 645, Folder 11)
- BRT (Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen), Publication (Box 645, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Report of the President, 1964; Publication (Box 645, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: Report of the Board of Appeals, 1964; Publication (Box 645, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: Report of the Board of Directors, 1964; Publication (Box 645, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: Report of the General Secretary and Treasurer, 1964; Publication (Box 645, Folder 12)
  - Item 5: Report of the Board of Trustees and Insurance, 1964; Publication (Box 645, Folder 12)
- BRT (Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen), Publication (Box 645, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the Thirty-Second Convention, 1964; Publication (Box 645, Folder 13)
- BRT (Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen), Publication (Box 646, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the Thirty-Third Convention, 1968; Publication (Box 646, Folder 1)
- BRAC (Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks), Publication (Box 646, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the Eleventh Regular and Third Triennial Convention, 1922; Publication (Box 646, Folder 2)
    Author: BRAC (Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks)
- BRAC (Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks), Publication (Box 646, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the Twelfth Regular and Fourth Triennial Convention, 1925; Publication (Box 646, Folder 3)
- BRAC (Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks), Publication (Box 646, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the Fourteenth Regular and Sixth Triennial Convention, 1931; Publication (Box 646, Folder 4)
- BRAC (Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks), Publication (Box 646, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the Fifteenth Regular and First Quadrennial Convention, 1935; Publication (Box 646, Folder 5)
- BRAC (Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks), Publication (Box 646, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the Sixteenth Regular and Second Quadrennial Convention, 1939; Publication (Box 646, Folder 6)
- BRAC (Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks), Publication (Box 646, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the Eighteenth Regular and Fourth Quadrennial Convention, 1947; Publication (Box 646, Folder 7)
- BRAC (Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks), Publication (Box 646, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the Nineteenth Regular and Fifth Quadrennial Convention, 1951; Publication (Box 646, Folder 8)
- BRAC (Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks), Publication (Box 646, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the Twentieth Regular and Sixth Quadrennial Convention, 1955; Publication (Box 646, Folder 9)
- BRAC (Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks), Publication (Box 646, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the Twenty-Firxt Regular and Seventh Quadrennial Convention, 1959; Publication (Box 646, Folder 10)
- BRAC (Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks), Publication (Box 646, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the Twenty-Second Regular and Eighth Quadrennial Convention, 1963; Publication (Box 646, Folder 11)
- Brotherhood of Railway Carmen of America, Publication (Box 646, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the Fourteenth Convention, 1921; Publication (Box 646, Folder 12)
    Author: Brotherhood of Railway Carmen of America
- Brotherhood of Railway Carmen of America, Publication (Box 646, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the Fifteenth Convention, 1925; Publication (Box 646, Folder 13)
- Brotherhood of Railway Carmen of America, Publication (Box 646, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the Sixteenth Convention, 1929; Publication (Box 646, Folder 14)
- Brotherhood of Railway Carmen of America, Publication (Box 646, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the Eighteenth Convention, 1941; Publication (Box 646, Folder 15)
- Brotherhood of Railway Carmen of America, Publication (Box 647, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the Nineteenth Convention, 1946; Publication (Box 647, Folder 1)
- Brotherhood of Railway Carmen of America, Publication (Box 647, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the Twentieth Convention, 1950; Publication (Box 647, Folder 2)
- Brotherhood of Railway Carmen of America, Publication (Box 647, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the Twenty-First Convention, 1954; Publication (Box 647, Folder 3)
- Brotherhood of Railway Carmen of America, Publication (Box 647, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the Twenty-Second Convention, 1958; Publication (Box 647, Folder 4)
- Brotherhood of Railway Carmen of America, Publication (Box 647, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the Twenty-Third Convention, 1963; Publication (Box 647, Folder 5)
- Brotherhood of Railway Carmen of America, Publication (Box 647, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the Twenty-Fifth Convention, 1973; Publication (Box 647, Folder 6)
- BSCP (Brotherhood of Sleeping Car Porters), Publication (Box 647, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Report of Proceedings of the Fourth Biennial Convention, 1944; Publication (Box 647, Folder 7)
    Author: BSCP (Brotherhood of Sleeping Car Porters)
    Notes: Nineteenth Anniversary Celebration
- BSCP (Brotherhood of Sleeping Car Porters), Publication (Box 647, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Report of Proceedings of the Fifth Biennial Convention, 1946; Publication (Box 647, Folder 8)
    Notes: Twenty-First Anniversary Celebration
- BSCP (Brotherhood of Sleeping Car Porters), Publication (Box 647, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Report of Proceedings of the Sixth Biennial Convention, 1948; Publication (Box 647, Folder 9)
    Notes: Twenty-Third Anniversary Celebration
- BSCP (Brotherhood of Sleeping Car Porters), Publication (Box 647, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Report of Proceedings of the Seventh Biennial Convention, 1950; Publication (Box 647, Folder 10)
    Notes: Silver Jubilee Celebration
- BSCP (Brotherhood of Sleeping Car Porters), Publication (Box 647, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Report of Proceedings of the First Triennial Convention, 1953; Publication (Box 647, Folder 11)
    Notes: Twenty-Eighth Anniversary Celebration
- BSCP (Brotherhood of Sleeping Car Porters), Publication (Box 647, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Report of Proceedings of the second Triennial Convention, 1956; Publication (Box 647, Folder 12)
    Notes: Thirty-First Anniversary Celebration
- Cloth Hat, Cap and Millinery Workers International Union, Publication (Box 647, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Report of Proceedings of the Fifteenth and Sixteenth Biennial Conventions, 1925-1927 (Box 647, Folder 13)
    Author: Cloth Hat, Cap and Millinery Workers International Union
- Cloth Hat, Cap and Millinery Workers International Union, Publication (Box 647, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Report of Proceedings of the Seventeenth Biennial Convention, 1929; Publication (Box 647, Folder 14)
- Cloth Hat, Cap and Millinery Workers International Union, Publication (Box 647, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Report of Proceedings of the Eighteenth Biennial Convention and Special Convention, 1933-1934 (Box 647, Folder 15)
- Federation of Federations Railway Employes, Publication (Box 648, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Official Proceedings of Convention, 1912; Publication (Box 648, Folder 1)
    Author: Federation of Federations Railway Employes
    Notes: April 15-23, 1912.
- AFL (American Federation of Labor). Railroad Employes' Department, Publication (Box 648, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Official Proceedings, 1914; Publication (Box 648, Folder 2)
    Author: AFL (American Federation of Labor). Railroad Employes' Department
    Notes: Second Biennial Convention. April 13-23, 1914.
- AFL (American Federation of Labor). Railroad Employes' Department, Publication (Box 648, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Official Proceedings, 1916; Publication (Box 648, Folder 3)
    Notes: Third Biennial Convention. April 10-21, 1916.
- AFL (American Federation of Labor). Railroad Employes' Department, Publication (Box 648, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Official Proceedings, 1918; Publication (Box 648, Folder 4)
    Notes: Fourth Biennial Convention. April 8-17, 1918.
- AFL (American Federation of Labor). Railroad Employes' Department, Publication (Box 648, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Official Proceedings, 1920; Publication (Box 648, Folder 5)
    Notes: Fifth Biennial Convention. April 12-21, 1920.
- AFL (American Federation of Labor). Railroad Employes' Department, Publication (Box 648, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Official Proceedings, 1922; Publication (Box 648, Folder 6)
    Notes: Sixth Biennial Convention. April 10-22, 1922.
- AFL (American Federation of Labor). Railroad Employes' Department, Publication (Box 648, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Official Proceedings, 1926; Publication (Box 648, Folder 7)
    Notes: Seventh Convention. June 28-July 2, 1926.
- AFL (American Federation of Labor). Railroad Employes' Department, Publication (Box 648, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Official Proceedings, 1930; Publication (Box 648, Folder 8)
    Notes: Eighth Convention. April 28-May 1, 1930.
- AFL (American Federation of Labor). Railroad Employes' Department, Publication (Box 648, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Official Proceedings, 1938; Publication (Box 648, Folder 9)
    Notes: Ninth Convention. April 4-8, 1938.
- AFL (American Federation of Labor). Railroad Employes' Department, Publication (Box 648, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Official Proceedings, 1951; Publication (Box 648, Folder 10)
    Notes: Tenth Convention. April 2-4, 1951.
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations). Railroad Employes' Department, Publication (Box 648, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Official Proceedings, 1956; Publication (Box 648, Folder 11)
    Author: AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations). Railroad Employes' Department
    Notes: Eleventh Convention. March 5-8, 1956.
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations). Railroad Employes' Department, Publication (Box 648, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Report of the Railway Employes' Department., 1957; Publication (Box 648, Folder 12)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations). Railroad Employes' Department, Publication (Box 648, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Official Proceedings, 1960; Publication (Box 648, Folder 13)
    Notes: Twelfth Convention. April 25-27, 1960.
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations). Railroad Employes' Department, Publication (Box 648, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Official Proceedings, 1964; Publication (Box 648, Folder 14)
    Notes: Thirteenth Convention. April 20-22, 1964.
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations). Railroad Employes' Department, Publication (Box 648, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Official Proceedings, 1968; Publication (Box 648, Folder 15)
    Notes: Fourteenth Convention. April 29-May 1, 1968.
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations). Railroad Employes' Department, Publication (Box 648, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Official Proceedings, 1972; Publication (Box 648, Folder 16)
    Notes: Fifteenth Convention. April 18-20, 1972.
- ILWU (International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union), Publication (Box 648, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the Eleventh Biennial Convention, 1955; Publication (Box 648, Folder 17)
    Author: ILWU (International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union)
    Notes: April 4-8, 1955.
- ILWU (International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union), Publication (Box 648, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the Twelfth Biennial Convention, 1957; Publication (Box 648, Folder 18)
    Notes: April 1-5, 1957.
- ILWU (International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union), Publication (Box 648, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the Thirteenth Biennial Convention, 1959; Publication (Box 648, Folder 19)
    Notes: April 6-13, 1959.
- ILWU (International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union), Publication (Box 648, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the Fourteenth Biennial Convention, 1961; Publication (Box 648, Folder 20)
    Notes: April 3-7, 1961.
- ILWU (International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union), Publication (Box 648, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the Fifteenth Biennial Convention, 1963; Publication (Box 648, Folder 21)
    Notes: April 1-5, 1963.
- ILWU (International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union), Publication (Box 648, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the Sixteenth Biennial Convention, 1965; Publication (Box 648, Folder 22)
    Notes: April 5-9, 1965.
- ILWU (International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union), Publication (Box 649, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the Seventeenth Biennial Convention, 1967; Publication (Box 649, Folder 1)
    Notes: April 3-7, 1967.
- ILWU (International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union), Publication (Box 649, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the Eighteenth Biennial Convention, 1969; Publication (Box 649, Folder 2)
    Notes: April 7-12, 1969.
- ILWU (International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union), Publication (Box 649, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the Nineteenth Biennial Convention, 1971; Publication (Box 649, Folder 3)
    Notes: April 19-23, 1971.
- ILWU (International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union), Publication (Box 649, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the Twentieth Biennial Convention, 1973; Publication (Box 649, Folder 4)
    Notes: April 30 to May 5, 1973.
- ILWU (International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union), Publication (Box 649, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the Twenty-First Biennial Convention, 1975; Publication (Box 649, Folder 5)
    Notes: April 7-12, 1975.
- International Fur and Leather Workers Union, Publication (Box 649, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the Nineteenth Biennial Convention, 1952; Publication (Box 649, Folder 6)
    Author: International Fur and Leather Workers Union
    Notes: May 11-17, 1952.
- AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 650, Folder 1)
- AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 650, Folder 2)
- AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 650, Folder 3)
- AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 650, Folder 4)
- AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 650, Folder 5)
- AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 650, Folder 6)
- AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 650, Folder 7)
- AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 650, Folder 8)
- AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 650, Folder 9)
- AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 650, Folder 10)
- AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 650, Folder 11)
- AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 650, Folder 12)
- AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 650, Folder 13)
- AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 650, Folder 14)
- AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 650, Folder 15)
- AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 650, Folder 16)
- AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 650, Folder 17)
- AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 650, Folder 18)
- AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 650, Folder 19)
- AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 650, Folder 20)
- AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 650, Folder 21)
- AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 650, Folder 22)
- AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 650, Folder 23)
- AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 650, Folder 24)
- AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 650, Folder 25)
- AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 650, Folder 26)
- AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 650, Folder 27)
- AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 650, Folder 28)
- AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 650, Folder 29)
- AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 650, Folder 30)
- AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 650, Folder 31)
- AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 651, Folder 1)
- AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 651, Folder 2)
- AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 651, Folder 3)
- AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 651, Folder 4)
- AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 651, Folder 5)
- AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 651, Folder 6)
- AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 651, Folder 7)
- AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 651, Folder 8)